

PROFILE

Hilam Lawrence Passens

I am a 33-year-old Software & Technical Engineer student, from Sandton, South Africa. I am passionate about system management, software development, and computer engineering. I have a background in Performing arts & graphic design. I am well experienced with facilitating children from toddlers to young adults as a former dance instructor.

I am in the market for a full-time position. I have an interest in working for a company that will be able to build on my skill set & provide opportunities to grow.

CONTACT

PHONE: +27 76 55 25 801

EMAIL:

lawrenceblood@gmail.com

HANDLES



REFERRALS



LAWRENCE PASSENS

IT SPECIALIST | PROGRAM DESIGNER | INTERN

EDUCATION

Mondale High Secondary School

Matriculant -2012 Focused subjects Mathematics, Physics & Biology.

College of Cape Town (City Campus)

Graphic Design - 2011 Short Course.

Intern Mecer



WORK EXPERIENCE

Owner of The Lifestyle Dance Center

2018-2022 Company founded and registered, been in practice since 2008, registered business in 201

Just You Artist & Model Management

2015-2017 Dance Director

33 & Me Talent Agency Private Dance Instructor/ Choreographer 2020- 2022 Dancer/Choreographer

SKILLS

- Interpersonal skills. Software Development. Programming.
- Communication skills.